Guide to the Philip M. Weightman Papers WAG.194
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education, 1949-1962.
  - Presidential Campaign, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Registration Statistics, 1960, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Republican Party, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Right-to-Work, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Woolfolk, Evelyn-Wolf, Law Business and Clerical Service, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Series III: General Correspondence, 1951-1967.
  - Abner, Willoughby, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - American Jewish Committee, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Barkan, Alexander E., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bartkin, Walter, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - CORE, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Earl W.,Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Earl W., Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Davis, Earl W., Reports, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Guernsey, George T., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Hill, Herbert, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Hobby, Wilbur, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - McDevitt, James L., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - McPeak, Carl, 1960, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Meany, George, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Neal, Fannie-Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Payne, Ethel, 1959, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Reuther, Roy L., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Schnitzler, William, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Taylor, Azie B., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Walker, W. Henry, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Webber, Charles C., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Weightman, Philip M.: Personal Papers, 1953, 1960-1966 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Series IV: Voter Registration, 1951-1967.
  - AFL-CIO Voter Registration Fund, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - COPE Conference on Registration, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - COPE, General, 1962-1967 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - COPE, Press Releases, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Elections, General (1952), 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - How Your Senators and Representatives Voted, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Mississippi, State of, Sample Ballot, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Mississippi Voter and Education League, Constitution and By-Laws, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - NAACP, General, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - NAACP State-by-State Breakdown of Voter Projects, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - NAACP Summer Projects in Voter Registration: AL, MS, SC, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - NAACP Summer Voter Registration Project, Weekly Report, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Negro Voter Registration in Southern States, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Negro Voting-Age Popul. throughout the United States, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Newark, New Jersey: Confidential Voting Registration Information, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Potential Vote (1958): State-by-State Estimates Produced by COPE Research Dept. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Potential Vote (1960): State-by-State Estimates Produced by COPE Research Dept (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Precinct Leader Training Manual, Illinois State CIO-PAC, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Precinct Workers Manual, Virginia Citizens’ Committees, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Presidential Election Results (1952) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Presidential Commission on Registration and Voting Participation, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Registration: Tract, Primer, and Guidebook on, 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Registration Program: Financial Reports, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Registration Program: Financial Material, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Registration Program: Manpower, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Registration Program: Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Registration Program: Politics, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Registration Program: Progress Reports, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Registration Program: Publicity, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Senatorial Election Results, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - South Carolina Voter Education Project, Proposed Budget, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Statistics, Registration, Election, etc., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Voter Registration in the South, Summer, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Voting Behavior of Negroes in Eleven States, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Voting Records of the House and Senate, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - What Happened in the South?, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - You Can Vote: Summaries of State Registration and Voting Laws, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Albuquerque, New Mexico Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Albany Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Boston Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Boston-Area Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Chicago Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chicago Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - COPE Area Conferences: Knoxville, Atlanta, Little Rock, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Denver Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Detroit Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Detroit-Area Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Houston Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Minneapolis Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - New York City-Area Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Norfolk, Virginia-Area Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Omaha Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Philadelphia Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Philadelphia-Area Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Pocatello, Idaho Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Sacramento, California Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - San Francisco Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Seattle Conference, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Seattle Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Washington, DC Conference, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Voter Registration-Alabama, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Voter Registration-Arkansas, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Voter Registration-District of Columbia, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Voter Registration-Florida, 1963, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Voter Registration-Georgia, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Voter Registration-Illinois, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Voter Registration-Indiana, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Voter Registration-Kansas, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Voter Registration-Kentucky, 1962, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Voter Registration-Louisiana, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Voter Registration-Maryland, 1960, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Voter Registration-Mississippi, 1963-1967 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Voter Registration-Missouri, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Voter Registration-New Jersey, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Voter Registration-New York, 1962, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Voter Registration-North Carolina, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Voter Registration-Ohio, 1962-1966 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Voter Registration-Oklahoma, 1962, 1964, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Voter Registration-Pennsylvania, 1960, 1963, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Voter Registration-South Carolina, 1963-1966 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Voter Registration-Virginia, 1962-1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Voter Registration-Tennessee, 1964, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Voter Registration-Texas, 1962-1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Voter Registration-Wisconsin, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Voter Registration-Washington, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Voter Registration-Wyoming, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Series V: Working Files, 1956-1962.
  - AFL-CIO Contacts, State-by-State Listings of, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - AFL-CIO-Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - AFL-CIO: Statements-Meany, 1959-1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Allen, Alexander J.: School Integration, a Community Challenge, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - American Council on Race Relations-Public Relations Program, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - American Friendship Club: Sixth Annual Human Rights Dinner, Program, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Armed Forces, 1945, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Association of Community Councils of Metropolitan Chicago, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Baptist Ministers and Churches of Philadelphia and Vicinity, Directory, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Benton, Senator William, Statement, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Biemiller, Andrew J.: Statements on Proposed Commission on Automation and Thirty-Five-Hour Work Week, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Chicago, South West Hyde Park Neighborhood Redevelopment Corp., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Citizens Council, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Civil Liberties, Current Developments, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - CIO: General, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - CIO-PAC: General Information, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - CIO-PAC: Shipment List, 1954-1955 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Colored Schools of Duval County (Florida), Director of Teachers, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Dorsey, Emmett E.: The American Negro and His Government, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Economic Situation of the Negroes in the United States, Notes on the, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, Establishing the President’s Committee on: Press Release, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Goodman, Leo: Various re: Atomic Energy, 1963, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Guide for Freedom School Leaders, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Henderson, Vivian W., The Economic Status of Negroes: In the Nation and in the South, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Henry, Aaron E., Address to Mississippi State Conference of the NAACP, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Highlander Research and Education Center, Inc.-Knoxville, Tennessee, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Institute on Non-Violence and Social Change, Program of Second Annual, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Jefferson County, Alabama, Elected Officials and Various, Civil Action Suit Brought Against, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Address on the Fourth Anniv. of the Montgomery Improvement Association, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Various, 1960, 1963, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - League for Universal Justice and Goodwill, undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Mississippi NAACP, Program of the 20th Session, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Monthly Office Expense Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - National Council of Negro Women, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - National Notes, Publication of the National Association of Colored Women, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Negro Baptist Denomination, 1956-1958 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Negro Business Associations in the United States, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Negro Newspapers in the United States, List of, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Negro Organizations, Convention Dates, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Negro Veterans and Servicemen, 1960 Audit of (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Negroes in the United States: Their Employment and Economic Status, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Open Occupancy in Housing Programs, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Payne, Ethel L., Medicare Issue Stirs Sharp Debate, undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Petition Submitted to Brigadier General Francis K. Newcomer, Governor, the Panama Canal, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Prayer Pilgrimage for Freedom, Lincoln Memorial, Washington DC, (four speeches), 1957 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Race Relations in Chicago, Report of the Mayor’s Commission on Human Relations, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Racial Integration in Education, National Conference on the Courts and: List of Delegates, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Racial Integration in Industry, Management Approaches to, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Real Unity (Newsletter, Swift Plant, Chicago), 1955 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Republican Party, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Right-to-Work, 1957-1967 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Right Wing Political Activities, 1951, 1964-1967 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Scammon Commission Recommendations, Summary of, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - South Carolina Labor Council: Convention Resolutions, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Southern Negro Voter Registration, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Taft-Hartley Act, Statement of Executive Board of the CIO on Senator Taft’s Proposed Amendments, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Tracts, Various, 1940s-1960s (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Truman, Harry S., Corruption in Congress: The Unpublicized Story, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - United States Information Agency, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - UTSE Newsletter, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Walker, Jack L., The Functions of Disunity: Negro Leadership in a Southern City, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Weightman, Philip M. and James E. Turner: Report on Minority Group Vote, 1954 Election (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1962 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Series VI: Newspaper Clippings and Press Releases, 1955-1967.
  - Africa-Angola, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Africa-Congo, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Africa-Editorial Comment, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Africa-General News (1), 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Africa-General News (2), 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Africa-Ghana, 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Africa-Guinea, 1960s (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Africa-Kenya, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Africa-MacMillan Tour, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Africa-Mboya, Tom, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Africa-Nkrumah, Kwame, 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Africa-Toure, Sekou, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Africa-Union of South Africa, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Africa-Jackie Robinson Story, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Black Muslims, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Chicago, Hyde Park Redevelopment, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Civil Rights-AFL-CIO Statements, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Civil Rights-Congress, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Civil Rights-General (1), 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Civil Rights-General (2), 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Civil Rights-General (3), 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Civil Rights-General (4), 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Civil Rights-General (5), 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Civil Rights-General (6), 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Civil Rights-General (7), 1956-1964 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Civil Rights-Housing, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Civil Rights-Incidents, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Civil Rights-Martin Luther King Jr., 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Civil Rights-President, 1960-1965 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Civil Rights-Sit-Ins, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Civil Rights-Supreme Court, 1959-1964 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Civil Rights Commission, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Discrimination-Sports, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - District Affairs, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Education, 1963-1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Elections-NSPC, 1955, 1960, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Freedom Rides, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Kennedy-Nixon Debates, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Khrushchev Visit, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Labor-General, 1957-1961 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Marshall, Thurgood, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - National Baptist Convention, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - National Legislation, 1957, 1960, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Negro in the North, Ashmore, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - New York City-Harlem, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Notes for Paper, CIO-PAC, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Peace Corps Plan, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Personalities, NSPC, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Populations Reports, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Racial Prejudice, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Reappointment, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Registration, NSPC, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Religious Issue, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Right-to-Work, NSPC, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - School Desegregation-Alabama, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - School Desegregation-Arkansas, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - School Desegregation-Court Action, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - School Desegregation-Georgia, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - School Desegregation-Louisiana, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - School Desegregation-Mississippi, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - School Desegregation-New York, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - School Desegregation-North Carolina, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - School Desegregation-Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - School Desegregation-South Carolina, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - School Desegregation-Tennessee, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - School Desegregation-Virginia, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - School Integration-General, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Segregation, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - South, The Integration Progress, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Voting Rights Bill (no. 1), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Voting Rights Bill (no. 2), 1965 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Voting Statistics-NSPC, 1950s (Box 9, Folder 39)